They're not partners. They're not friends. They're wolfs.
Wolfs is a crime, comedy film directed by Jon Watts.
Hired to cover up a high-profile crime, a fixer soon finds his night spiralling out
of control when he's forced to work with an unexpected counterpart.
Margaret's Man, played by George Clooney.
Pam's Man, played by Brad Pitt.
Kid, played by Austin Abrams.
Margaret, played by Amy Ryan.
June, played by Poorna Jagannathan.
Dimitri, played by Zlatko Burić.
Wolfs is a 2024 American action comedy film written and directed by Jon Watts.
Starring George Clooney, Brad Pitt, and Austin Abrams, it follows two nameless, professional fixers who
are forced to work together on a job despite their preference to operate as lone wolves.
Wolfs premiered out of competition at the Venice International Film
Festival on September 1, 2024, to lukewarm reviews.
It had a one-week limited theatrical release starting on September 20, 2024, it received mixed reviews from critics,
and was released a week after on Apple TV+, where it became the streaming service's most-viewed film.
Apple's decision to pivot the film to streaming despite pre-arranged agreements for a theatrical release led Watts not to move forward with a planned
sequel.However, Sony Pictures (through Columbia Pictures) retains the distribution rights to the film for its Video on-demand release.
The film explores themes of hotel room, dark
comedy, lone wolf, drugs, buddy comedy.
The tone is lighthearted and dark.